mrbutton.in 2019-01-08

# Privacy Policy - MR BUTTON

**

We value the trust you hold in MR BUTTON. Please read the following privacy policy carefully. While using and/or accessing our website you acknowledge that you read, understand and agree to be bound to all the terms mentioned in this privacy policy and other pages of this website.  
Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without/with notice. The revised privacy policy is effective immediately when posted on the website. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this privacy policy periodically for your reference.

**1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information Name, Email Address, Phone Number, shipping and billing address from you when you make a purchase with MR BUTTON. We do use your contact information to send you promotional and/or timely based offers.

**2\. Use of Demographic and Profile Data**  
We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. Your information is also used to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online offers, products, services and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. In our efforts to continuously improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users’ activity on our website. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

**3\. Cookies**  
A “cookie” is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. MR BUTTON places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer’s hard drive. MR BUTTON cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.  
Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven’t changed your computer’s settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the website. You can also delete your browser cookies or disable them entirely. But this may significantly impact your experience with our website and may make parts of our website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that you leave them turned on.

**4\. Sharing of Personal Information**  
We may share personal information with other corporate entities and affiliates to: help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate, related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and/or to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.  
We may disclose personal information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms and/or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.  
MR BUTTON will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur, that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

**5\. Security Precautions**  
Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

**6\. Advertising**  
We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, email address or any personally identifying information about the user.

**
